

Dmytro Pasichko

Python Full Stack Developer

Ukraine

+380500310835 · dmitry.pasichko@gmail.com

😑 LinkedIn, Telegram

Date of birth 15.08.1997

Languages English (B1)

Ukrainian (Native)

Skills SQL

Python

Problem Solving

Communication

Responsibility

Experience

- Invoicing
- Webhook
- Deployment
- Data Analysis
- Data collecting
- API Integration
- Data migrations
- Row SQL-queries
- AWS EC2 application
- Supervisor processes • DB's stored procedures

- **Event based Integration** • Asynchronous Integration

Profile

I am a highly motivated software developer. I have experience in both creating and maintaining real business applications (BSS, ERP, BI and Backend), as well as experience in QA automation.

I am confident that I am able to help achieve goals and be useful to the company.

Tools

Pycharm, bash, psql, curl, DBeaver, Swagger, Postman, Lens, kubectl, aws-cli, Slack

Employment History

Python Software Developer, QA Madness, Remote

December 2020 — Present

Responsibility:

- · Incident review
- System configuration
- · Cross-team communication
- Scrum, Kanban based work process
- · Technical analysis, clarification of business requirements
- · Feature developing, bug-fixes, optimization, refactoring and support
- Implement and optimize CI\CD, backup processes together with DevOps

Description:

Develop and support delivery applications from BSS, ERP, BI and Backend sides.

- Kafka Integration
- Unifonic SMS Integration
- Web cabinet development
- E-invoicing with CSV, XML, PDF reports
- Incoming and outgoing email processing
- Applying designed templates to public and cabinet pages

Tech stack:

- SQLAlchemy, Pandas, NumPy, Confluent Kafka
- Python, Odoo, Django, Django Rest Framework, HTML, CSS, JS
- Redis, Kafka, PostgreSQL, AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Nginx, Git

QA Automation Engineer, QA Madness, Kharkiv

August 2019 — December 2020

Responsibility:

· Load, Functional, Integration, UI Testing

- Write testing documentation, create bugs
- Discussion with dev team and product team about system behavior

Description:

Testing, analyzing and implementing QA process to CI/CD. Prepare test reports and writing test documentation for all levels of software testing.

Tech stack:

• Java: Spring, Selenide, Selenium, TestNG

JS: Cypress Python: PyTest

PHP Back-End Developer, PsSoft, Dnipro

September 2016 — August 2017

Responsibility:

- System configuration
- Scrum, Kanban based work process
- Technical analysis, clarification of business requirements
- Feature developing, bug-fixes, optimization, refactoring and support

Description:

Development of web applications for corporate and commercial clients

Tech stack:

• PHP, Laravel, Zend, HTML, CSS, JS.

Education

Bachelor degree at «Software engineering», Dnepropetrovsk National University of Railway Transport, Dnipro, Ukraine;

September 2016 – June 2019

Junior Bachelor at «Software engineering», Dnirpo technical school of of welding and electronics, Dnipro, Ukraine;

September 2012 – June 2016